Music plays I look up to the
stars and reach for the sky.
I believe in tomorrow if we try!
Hey!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music!
We share the music!
Come on, let's go, baby, baby!
Oh, we share the one dream!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the good times!
We share the good times!
Let's go, baby, baby, oh
we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me!
Through the darkness
that is in this world?
So hard to see or to believe!
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we
Feel the rush brought up by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat!
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the time, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what!
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go!
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try high!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top we go, one straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good!
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I Share
the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what!
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go!
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try!
I know that you are there!
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me!
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go!
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
We owe you our lives!
We won't forget what
you've done, Straw Hat.
Thank you for giving us the sun!
Take care!
Don't get annihilated out there!
That would be very bad!
Why did you even say that?
Are you out of your mind?
Bye, Lola, and thanks for the
fever card! I'll miss you!
I hope we meet again someday!
If you see my mama, tell
her I said hi, Nomizo!
Let's go!
Sensei!
Well, I guess they're gone now.
Yeah
Looks like the fog's come back.
We set sail tomorrow!
Roger!
No one knows the truth behind what
happens in the Sea of Mysteries.
The Florian Triangle.
Each year, over a hundred ships sail
into the mists, never to return!
The giant ship Thriller Bark first dropped
anchor in these dark waters ten years ago.
But the tales of terror and
disappearances came long before then.
Perhaps it is fortunate that the thick
mist is abundant on this day as well,
cloaking the terrors of these
mysterious waters like a white veil.
Luffy huh you sure you're okay with this
huh oh right you mean i use this paper
It'll be fine don't worry about it
Luffy we can take a detour
if you like i wouldn't mind
Time has proven to be no obstacle
to either me or Laboon so
long as i draw breath i know
we'll be Reunited someday yeah
it's fine you do what you want
captain we don't care one bit
yeah i'm ready To go everywhere
wow i want to meet luffy's bro
in the big whale bro seriously
it's okay even if Ace wasn't
some kind of trouble he wouldn't
want his little brother to
come bail him out that drive
Him crazy he hates to show his
weak side and he never asked for
help if i saved his life he'd
probably just get mad.
As pirates, we're supposed
to be rivals anyway.
His adventures are his
business, even if they turn out bad.
Well, keep your hopes up.
Lola's pals were saying the card doesn't
just shrink when someone's in trouble.
It also grows bigger if
things get better for them.
Good.
Then I'll see him again when
he's back to full strength.
I'm sure that's what he was
thinking when he gave me that card, right?
Oh yeah, Zoro.
You were asleep for the big party,
so I guess you missed out on this.
Well, no harm in doing
it one more time, right?
Let's all raise our mouths in celebration
of our newest crew member, the musician,
Brooke!
Cheers!
Really, you're too kind.
Full speed ahead!
Let's get moving with
the Coup de Burst! Yeah!
Coup de Burst!
We're flying!
What's going on?
Oh, oh, oh! Oh!
Bartholomew Kuma has returned, sir!
This is a joke!
How is it that even with your power,
you couldn't stop the
Straw Hatch from escaping?
I'm the one who has to
explain this to the top brass,
so your story better be damn good.
That's my grandson for ya.
I don't want to hear it, Garp.
You were ordered to exterminate
every pirate on Thriller Bark,
but you failed to even breathe
back Straw Hat Luffy's head.
This is a disgrace.
Don't worry about it, Sengoku.
Sure, Luffy brought down Moria, but he
ain't gonna go around blabbing about it.
Who would believe him anyway?
I hope you didn't take pity on those pirates
just because they were injured, Kuma.
Compassion is wasted on them.
It won't make them change
their course one bit.
And speaking of course, if they
keep following their long pose,
they'll be on the doorstep of
Navy headquarters in no time.
Oh, hey, I got this fancy pants
tea I've been wanting to try.
Break out some crackers.
Don't wait a sec, Garp!
That's enough!
It's a sea snake current!
Okay, but what is that?
Brace yourselves!
We can do this, you guys!
comes you better steer the ship right
Oh, we made it out!
Yeah, well, I wasn't scared.
We're finally here!
We made it!
I can't even see the top!
It's huge!
So this is the red line!
It's strange.
It feels sort of nostalgic.
I'm getting a bit choked up.
It hasn't been that long since we last
saw this, but I feel like we've grown up.
I can't seem to stop crying.
Guess a lot's happened, huh?
Anyway, we're halfway there.
The twin capes where we
met Laboon are connected
to the red line on the
other side of the world.
We've had some close calls, but I'm glad
we made it this far without losing anybody.
When I was a baby, I came to the
South Blue Down Reverse Mountain.
But that was well over 30 years ago.
The red line means a lot
more to me this time.
I came from the west blue to
this ocean five years ago,
but it seems like forever now.
If we keep this up and sail
around the rest of the world,
we'll come to this wall one more time.
And when we do, then I'm
gonna be king of the pirates!
We have to be extra
careful from here on out.
We're right next to the
holy land of Marijua,
home of Navy headquarters
and the world government.
How did we ever live
without a swimming pool?
I'm still too weak.
I won't be powerless again!
I won't let myself be weak.
I won't fail my crew?
Okay, Robin, Brooke,
Luffy, do you see anything?
No use.
It's pitch black.
Yep, pitch black!
Wait, no, I think I just saw something.
A monster!
Its eyes were glowing in the dark!
Did he say monster?
We're gonna die!
No, I suppose I'm already dead, aren't I?
Oh, that reminds me, Nami.
I have a dying request.
Would you be so kind as to tell me
what kind of panties you're wearing?
You want a monster?
I'll show you one!
For a skeleton, he sure has guts.
Shark Suburge 3 has a max
depth of 5,000 meters,
So be careful you don't get
yourself in trouble down there.
That's odd.
I don't imagine it's supposed to
make that horrid creaking noise.
Oh, no. That's bad.
I'm afraid we already passed 5,000 meters.
That makes sense.
Oh.
Wait, that is bad.
The water pressure's going to
crush the submarine like a tin can.
Hey, it's that monster again.
I think he likes us.
My, what big teeth he has.
That was brutal.
He thinks we're food.
Here it comes again.
So are they in trouble or not?
I don't think I ever want to ride
in Shark Submerge 3. No kidding.
Nami Swan!
I made a nice tart with horror
pears I found on Thriller Bark.
It sounds scary, but I promise it's yummy.
Ooh, I can't wait to try it!
Ah!
Look, it's behind us! Whoa!
It's gonna eat us! Cool!
This really is a mess, huh?
Oh, that's yummy!
So good!
I thought we knew where we were
going, but it's like Skypiea all over.
No kidding.
Even if we know which direction to go,
that doesn't tell us how to get there.
Give me a break, Fishman Island.
Where are you?
We're back!
Oh, my!
Was that ever fun!
Nice job staying alive, you guys.
For all the good it did me, I
couldn't see a thing down there.
Are you sure this is
where Fishman Island's at?
No loss for me.
I'd gladly do that again.
We'd have gone farther down, but the
water pressure would have crushed us.
I don't know what else to do.
The Log Pose is definitely
pointing straight down.
What a pain.
It's too late now, but I should
have asked Lola how this works.
Whoa!
It's a monster!
If you think you can beat me out of
the water, you're in for a surprise.
Gumbum!
Rifle!
You know what?
It doesn't seem all that big.
We did just fight oars.
Now everything's gonna seem small.
Hey, something flew out of its mouth.
A fish A girl
Wait,
is that I think so Oh,
hell yes Ah! Ah!
Ah!
I crushed a human, oh no!
I'm sorry.
Are you OK? OK.
Of course I'm OK.
Never been better anyway.
How are you doing?
Pull yourself together!
That's a tail!
No, he must have hit his head.
He's acting weird.
With fins?
Maybe you should lie down.
Then that means she's a...
A mermaid!
Huh?
Oh my gosh, there's a bunch of humans!
Uh, yeah.
Okay, let's all stop screaming.
I'm sorry, I was just startled.
Anyway, thanks for saving my life.
It feels like I'm always
getting swallowed by sea kings.
This was probably the 20th time.
You gotta stop that. Jeez.
There has to be some way
to pay you guys back.
Oh, octopus fritters.
You have some?
Ooh, give me, give me.
Sure thing.
They're 500 berries each.
How many can I put you down for?
You're not selling them.
I'm not, am I?
I finally met a real mermaid.
Mermaids!
Loved by sailors the whole world wide!
Mermaids, the jewels of the sea!
And she's adorable, just like I imagined!
I'm kidding, you're even
better than I imagined!
You said your name was Kuma?
This is the best day of my whole life!
Come on, that's not true.
Remember?
You met Granny Kokoro, didn't you?
Gigantic monsters.
Zombies. That was nothing.
That's not fear.
My heart already felt the true
meaning of terror when I saw her.
It's okay.
I know just how you feel.
Let's just forget that
ever happened, Sanji.
She's the first mermaid we've met.
Could you be any more rude? Huh?
Are you saying that Granny
Kokoro was a mermaid?
But she could walk and stuff. I see.
Guess you never found out, did you?
You were busy fighting that luchi
guy when she saved us from drowning.
Everyone, breathe!
Don't you die on me!
Granny Kokoro was cool and all, but thinking
of her as a mermaid is really gross.
You'll be old someday, too!
That hurt!
Why are you so strong?
Jeez, I've had enough of you men
and your gross mermaid fantasies.
But still, she is rather cute, isn't she?
This is my first encounter
with a mermaid as well.
Pardon me, but would you be so
kind as to lend me some money?
What the hell, Brooke?
Skeletons!
Now you're scaring her, you big freak!
Get out of here!
Hey, I can open my head!
Pretty cool, huh?
That is cool!
And now she's fine.
So I gotta know, how do you poop?
What is wrong with you?
Oh, poop, yeah.
She doesn't poop!
You're the one pooping here! Hey, Kuma.
Hello, Kuma.
Aren't you forgetting someone?
Like a friend that you might have neglected
to include in your fun little chat?
Someone like me?
So, uh, one question,
Kuma, what is this thing?
Like, uh, talking glove, maybe?
Oh, no, no, this guy is my pet.
His name is Papa Goo.
He's a starfish and also my teacher.
This guy? Yep.
What's up?
Is it normal for starfish to talk?
As normal as it is for your
pet to be your teacher.
I let her take me in.
We have our reasons.
Kuma!
She feeds me clams.
What can I say?
I am what I am.
That's your pet food?
A starfish is a star.
And when people don't know
who you are, it's so rough.
Will I stick around?
Well, I'm no sucker, but my
suckers are sicky enough.
Does anybody need a hand don't sweat
I've got plenty but as for fingers baby?
Cakes I don't got any no
fingers yeah thanks everybody!
Come on this is the part You guys
are supposed to laugh my t-shirt
is made by criminal they're a
really popular Fashion label on fish
man island that's pretty cool and
papa goo is their lead designer I
want To be one too someday so that's
why he's teaching me you can do it
whatever it is you can do it Oh thanks
that's so sweet of you you can be
a model too you should put on a
fashion show for us Oh no I don't think
so glove guy how can you talk I'm
so glad you asked he got over that
one quick See back when I was a kid
I was a little confused I thought I
was a human but by the Time I figured
out I was a starfish I already
knew how to talk well I didn't know
talking worked Like that the brain
is a powerful thing my friend they
say you can do anything you put your
mind to Anyway whatever I'm papa goo
the starfish up and coming fashion
designer thanks for saving me
Seriously you guys are the best we're
lucky we met you the truth is we're
a bit lost since you're From around
here no nami octopus fighters first
right I forgot I won't charge you
either hold on Let me call Hatchan
and we'll work out a meeting spot.
Who is Hatchan?
Hey, it's Kuma.
Are you doing okay, Hatchan?
Sorry I got kind of lost.
So where are you right now?
Oh, so it's Kuma, is it?
Hatchan?
You don't know who you're talking to.
This ain't your buddy, Hatchan.
You're not Hatchan!
Of course not.
Listen, this is Macro from
the Big Dumb Macro Gang.
Wait, I shouldn't say that myself.
My goodness, this sounds like trouble.
What are you doing with
Hotchen's transponder, snail?
We beat him up and stole it from him.
What do you think?
You're right.
Don't lie to me.
There's no way Hatchan would lose to you.
Normally, you'd be right.
We aren't really a match for him.
But this time, we teamed up
with the Flying Fish Riders,
and he didn't stand a chance.
The Flying Fish Riders, damn it! You!
Kuma, you're all right.
Well, that's a relief.
Hatchan, don't tell me
they really beat you.
You, I got my guard down.
Anyway, no matter what they
tell you, don't come to save me.
I'll beat these guys somehow
and get out on my own.
I'll meet up with you
later, so don't worry.
Hatchan.
You know, Kuma, we were planning
on selling your friend here.
Octopus Fishman bet you a high price, so
if you want to save him, You better hurry.
Oh, for the record, we're
at the Sabo Odi Archipelago,
five kilometers east of Grove 44.
And did I fail to mention this is
the Flying Fish Riders' hideout?
Because it is.
I'm telling you, Kuma, don't come here!
Shut up, sucker face, no one cares!
Ha, see you there.
Oh, Hatchan.
So, the fritters?
This isn't the time for that!
Hold on a second.
Her friend on the transponder's
snail sounds awfully familiar to me,
and they said he was an octopus fish man.
Hmm, it's my imagination.
There's no way, right?
Sorry, Luffy-chin, but can I give you
your octopus fritters some other time?
It's just that I have to save
my friend before it's too late.
Oh!
Hey! So, Kuma,
I know this might come
across as meddlesome,
but if you're going to rescue your
friend, you don't have to do it alone.
You can leave that to us.
Wait, I said that wrong.
What I meant is that you
can leave it to them!
You're not our boss in return.
You can show us the way to
fish man island Which is a
good deal since you're probably
headed back there anyway.
Are you sure really?
Of course Right Luffy huh?
Sure you'll beat up all the bad
guys for me Luffy chin really
and you'll save hot chin I guess
but who is this hot chin guy?
He runs the octopus
fritter shop where I work
He makes the best snacks
in the world promise.
We're gonna save those octopus fritters
even if it kills us you hear me?
Octopus snacks!
Well, now that they're motivated,
can you show me the way?
Let me see.
Grove 44 is a tiny island right here
on the east edge of the archipelago.
Based at five kilometers east from there.
So I'm guessing the Flying Fish
Riders base is in this area.
As for us, we're about here right now.
So if we head due west towards
Sabaody, we'll hit it on the way.
BAM simple as can be we
can have some fish for
directions before we set
off right sounds good
Look!
All the fish are coming up!
We need directions from you!
You! You! You!
They're scared of the flying fish riders,
so they won't get too close,
but they will show us the way.
Oh, wow.
I didn't know you could talk to fish.
Maybe the men are right.
Mermaids are really something.
You know, if you stick around, we can
eat all the fish in the whole world.
You need a timeout? Huh?
Watch your mouth.
Hmm, but one thing is bugging me.
How are we supposed to follow fish?
Check it out for yourself.
Whoa! Awesome!
And I guess fish are a lot smarter
than I give them credit for.
See?
Check it out.
They're drawing an arrow in the water.
Perfect.
We shouldn't have any
problem following that.
That's just wow. So cool. Oh, stop.
Any mermaid could do the same thing.
Don't be so modest.
We don't know any better.
Okay, I'm going to take the help.
Four o 'clock, Usopp.
Got it.
Hey, Zoril.
I noticed the sun is setting off.
Did we finally find a
way to Fishman Island?
Forget that.
Check it out.
It's a real-life mermaid.
Her name's Kuma.
Isn't she cool?
Nice to meet you.
She's a mermaid, huh?
Never seen one before.
It's gone!
He erased his memory!
He has a friend that makes
real good octopus fritters,
so we're going to save
him first so we can eat.
I'm kind of worried.
Hatchan didn't sound like
himself at all when they talked.
I'm afraid they've done
something awful to him.
Eh, he's tough enough to cope.
I wouldn't worry about it.
You guys, on the other hand, were
awful quick to offer your help,
but are you positive you're
not in over your head on this?
You kidding?
All right.
Well, fair warning.
These guys aren't the only
kidnappers in the area.
There's a whole bunch
of crews just like him.
The Sabaody Archipelago is
a hotspot for kidnapping.
Human trafficking is big
business around here.
You mean like slave trading or something?
Pretty sick stuff.
And seeing as mermaids fetch
a high price on the market,
A trio of fishmen that
call themselves the Macro
Gang have been targeting
Kuma for a long time.
We were stuck in that sea
monster's belly for a while.
Hachi probably got worried
about us and figured
the Macro Gang kidnapped you or something.
Then he went after them to rescue
you and got kidnapped himself.
Yeah, that must be it
Hutchin's so kind, and he's
always looking after me.
This is all my fault!
Guys named Hatchan, huh?
Reminds me that dumbass
octopus from way back.
If it's that guy, there's
no way I'm helping him.
But what are the odds, right?
Usually Hachi can take those guys,
or anybody else for that matter.
But with the flying fish riders
involved, it's a whole different story.
Okay, but who are these guys?
They're another one of those
kidnapping crews I mentioned.
They've really been
running the place lately.
Word is, once they target you,
you're as good as done for.
Their boss Devil is this
scary guy with an iron mask.
Nobody knows what his face looks like.
Anyway, it seems like
they're looking for someone.
They've been stopping
every ship that comes by
here and checking out their
crews member by member.
Man, they sound like a real pain!
Eh, how tough can they be?
It's fine Don't worry, Kuma,
we'll get the octopus fritters back
for sure That's fritters salesman?
I, I'm sure you're right, luffy chin?
Of course I'm right!
Hey, Brooke, why don't you play
a song to lighten the mood?
With pleasure, Captain.
What hey guys we're in trouble!
Did something happen?
What's the matter?
The fish said they're sorry.
But they can't take us any further.
They're scared.
Wait, what? Someone's here? Ah! Look!
It's the Flying Fish Riders!
Where?
I can't see anything!
Kate! Katie!
Where are you going?
You have to hide!
They're in the sky, not the sea! Look up!
Wow, they really can fly!
That's awesome!
They're our enemy, remember?
Damn it, attacking his head on?
They have seats and
hammawars and everything!
Hey, it's them! Yeah, you're right.
Those are the Straw Hat Pirates
down there, no doubt about it.
Let's contact the boss. You got it.
I thought we'd only make
it out with the mermaid.
This is our lucky day!
Hey, Master Duvall's gonna be
thrilled when he hears this.
Here they come again!
They're dropping bombs. Jerks! Come on!
72 caliber! Let's go!
That was a close one.
They're not finished.
Once they're out of the water, flying fish
can stay in the air up to five minutes.
Yep, that's right, Master Devil.
There's no doubt in my
mind that it's them.
Huh? Wait.
Sorry, sir, I missed that last part.
Turn around.
He told us to go back to base.
But that's ridiculous.
Boss's orders. Who knows?
Fine, but I don't get it.
They're gone?
Mackerel.
What is it, Master Devil?
That mermaid you were luring here
is on a pirate ship right now.
Were you aware of that? Huh? Kuma? No!
The very pirate ship I've been
searching for all this time.
All my suffering.
All my waiting.
will finally come to an
end i'll have my revenge
i'll kill that bastard that ruined my life